Curriculum Vitae

Mr. Morgan Wilson-Slider Telephone: +44 (0)7759 782850

Email: mwilsonslider1234@outlook.com

An enthusiastic and dedicated individual who has a mature and responsible approach to situations, as a calm and professional person. I have great communication skills that enables me to work within a team environment, but I am also confident in working individually and remotely. I have experience with vast aspects of the developmental process, this is through 5+ years of experience. I have learned a great deal with at designing, creating, and testing web-based applications.

Key Skills

- Leadership, Management, Researching and Reporting skills.
- Project Management (Agile and Waterfall)
- Database management (MySQL, Apache)
- Windows and Linux (Command Prompt, PowerShell (git)) (Parrot, Terminal)
- Software skills (Visual Studio 2022/2019, NetBeans, VMware, Cisco Packet Tracer, VSCode, Google Apps)
- Web development Skills (SelectCommerce (CMS), WordPress)
- Networking(Switches, Routing Protocols, LAN & WAN, VPN, Network Packet Analysis, Network Design, IP(TCP / IP / DNS / DHCP) Troubleshooting, Server Administration).
- Network Security (Stateful Firewalls, Juniper Firewalls, Packet Tracing).
- General Security (Virus and Malware Management)
- AI (Juniper)
- Coding Languages (JavaScript, Java, HTML, CSS, C, C#, C++, PHP, Ajax, SQL, Git, R, Node-JS, Playwright, .Net,)
- · Customer Service.

Career Summary

2022 - Present: We Heart Digital (Technical Assistant).

Key responsibilities: Administration, Quality Assurance, Customer Support and Web-Developing (Full Stack). This role has allowed me to gain work related experience within a developer role, as well as building upon my confidence with coding languages and develop new coding languages.

I have a diverse role that I easily adapt to daily, allowing me to work on Large/Small eCommerce websites, as well as working closely with other companies and giving me insights into how these companies work with each-other.

2021 - 2022: Curry's PC World (Sales Adviser).

Key responsibilities: Assisting customers select products that fits their needs and offer IT support where necessary. The main aim of working at Curry's PC World was to gain work experience, and to gain some knowledge on hardware, connectivity and to gain customer service skills.

Education

Batcheler's of Science (Hons) Computer and Information Security.

A-Levels – Information Computing Technology, Applied Science, Sociology.

GCSEs - Mathematics, English Language, English Literature, Science, Psychology, Food Technology, Resistant Materials, Information Computing Technology.

2017 - 2021: University of Plymouth. BSc (Hons) Computer and Information Security.

Key Knowledge: The experience of university has allowed me to further my understanding of the theory behind a lot of areas and has allowed me to better understand the practice of different methodologies. The course followed closely alongside the legal and ethical systems. I graduated a year ago and always am able to provide my certificate upon request.

Personal Interests

I host a dungeon and dragons' campaign which allows me to discuss and solve issues, this has helped me develop both creativity and team communication. Through this I have learned a lot of skills necessary for my character and creative growth. I often plan a lot of the scenarios and take leadership, as such this has helped me develop my skills in, software, leadership, resource management, mathematics, preparation, planning, experimentation, and visualization skills. The game also has helped me to mediate people who often have strong conflicting opinions.

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/morgan-wilson-slider-411b39222/

References available upon request.